## **BRAD MYRICK**

- E brad.myrick@proton.me
- Portfolio Portfolio
- **W** Github
- **W** Twitter

US Army Veteran and Web3 focused Software Engineer open to contract or full-time roles within organizations that are pushing the bounds of technology forward. I bring unique life and work experiences as well as a proven ability to adapt to and overcome new challenges. Please consider me for any roles for which my skills would be useful.

## **EDUCATION**

**B.SC: COMPUTER SCIENCE, FULL SAIL UNIVERSITY** - Salutatorian - Advanced Achievement Award Recipient

**DCBC COMERCIAL DIVER, CDA TECHNICAL INSTITUTE** - One of only two US schools that offer the Diver Certification Board of Canada's validation and licensing. - NDT level 2 certified - Scuba Dive Master certified (extracurricular)

## **EXPERIENCE**

**2022 - PRESENT SYSTEM ENGINEER, TRUGARD.IO** - Build complex ETL backend systems in GO lang that parse EVM blockchains and extract data from deployed contracts, wallets, and transactions - Decompile and inspect bytecode, pushing information to a GraphDB - Work with Google Cloud, Kubernetes, kserve, Go, Python, OVH, and QuickNode

**2019 - 2022 SOFTWARE ENGINEER, TACVUE.IO** / **KODR.PRO** - Web3 DApp and Solidity Smart Contract design and deployment - Moralis DB and Cloud Function implementation - NFT Trait Assembly with Whitelisting and Mint-Site integration - AWS Cloud management and API design

**2014 – 2019 DIVER FOREMAN, UNDERWATER CONSTRUCTION CORP** - NDT in water inspection and repair of US Nuclear power facilities - Ensure diver safety and OSHA divesite compliance - Perry Nuclear Deep Dive Team member

**2005 – 2012 US ARMY SERGEANT / DOD CONTRACTOR, M109A6 TECH -** Convoy Protection Team Lead - Iraq 2008 -2009 - Foreign Military Technical Trainer, DOD Iraq 2011 - 2012

## **CERTIFICATIONS & SKILLS**

- BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE
- EJPT CERTIFICATION IN ETHICAL HACKING
- DATA VIS AND MACHINE LEARNING / SKLEARN
- PYTHON / SOLIDITY / GO
- ANDROID DEVELOPMENT / ANDROID STUDIO
- VERSION CONTROL / GIT
- LABRIE AUTOMATED SYSTEMS CODING AND REPAIR COURSE
- DIVER CERTIFICATION BOARD OF CANADA (D.C.B.C.) QUALIFIED AS AN UNRESTRICTED SURFACE SUPPLIED COMMERCIAL DIVER
- NON-DESTRUCTIVE TESTING (N.D.T.) LEVEL I & II U/W V.T., U.T. & M.P.I.